Jack Isaacs

67 Wellington Road, Crowthorne, Berkshire, RG45 7LJ

Mobile: 07887530357

Jackisaacs97@gmail.com

PROFILE

A highly motivated individual who specialises in problem solving and team working skills. Obtained A levels in Computing, Graphic Product Design and a level 3 Diploma in ICT. An advanced knowledge of Computers and Graphic design acquired through academic and professional experience. Communicative, and hardworking, and up to any task given.

EDUCATION

2008 – 2013: Edgbarrow School, Crowthorne:

12 GCSEs A*- C including computing, Maths, and Graphic Design.

2008 – 2015: Edgbarrow Sixth Form, Crowthorne:

A Level Product Design: B A Level Computer Science: C

Level 3 BTEC ICT: Distinction* Distinction*

2015 – 2018: Southampton Solent University, Southampton:

BSc Computer Games (Software Development)

At Solent, I have acquired invaluable interpersonal and technical skills. In my first year of the course there was a broad spectrum of units catered to all essences of game development which allowed us to figure out what we were really good at.

In my second year, we started focusing on the nitty-gritty aspects of development. Using SDL and conducting a fully thought out design, testing and implementation of a prototype game. In my second semester, we started using PS4 development kits to create and implement a simple platformer game prototype from scratch.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Upwork

Freelancer – November 2015 to Present Part time game development and graphic design outsourcing for international clients. Regus – Ancells Business Park, Fleet, 01252 761000

Cleaner – July 2016 to September 2016
Day to day office cleaning including bathrooms and kitchens.

The Golden Fry – Crowthorne, Berkshire, 01344 778683

Cashier – January 2015 to September 2015 Serving customers and packaging fried food.

SKILLS

- C++ Programming (2 years' exp.)
 - SDL 2
 - SFML 2.4
 - PS4 SDK 2.5
- · Unity, C# (5 years' exp.)
- · Python (4 years' exp.)
 - Tkinter
 - Pygame
 - · SQLite3
- · GitHub version control
- · HTML
- JavaScript
- Game Design
- · Oracle APEX (5 months exp.)
- Team working, interpersonal and punctuality skills
- · Excellent debugging and problem solving skills
- Object-Oriented Development
- · Multithreaded systems
- · Blender
- · Low-res pixel art & animation
- · Adobe Photoshop
- · Adobe Illustrator

HOBBIES

I love to keep fit and have been part of a large mountain biking group in my hometown for many years, cycling locally and afar on weekend trips to Exmoor, Wales, and the South Downs. Mountain biking has been a big part of my life and I have been doing it for as long as I can remember.

I have been an on-and-off guitarist for around 5 years, and is something I really hope to get into properly.